<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Aryuze&#39;s site</title>
  
  
  <link href="https://aryuze.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://aryuze.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2025-07-06T09:28:21.485Z</updated>
  <id>https://aryuze.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Ayz</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Looooong Update</title>
    <link href="https://aryuze.github.io/2025/06/27/abc/"/>
    <id>https://aryuze.github.io/2025/06/27/abc/</id>
    <published>2025-06-27T12:31:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2025-07-06T09:28:21.485Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<link rel="stylesheet" class="aplayer-secondary-style-marker" href="\assets\css\APlayer.min.css"><script src="\assets\js\APlayer.min.js" class="aplayer-secondary-script-marker"></script><p>it’s been a super long time after the last update<br>because i was busy constructing the main part of my website<br>so i didn’t have any time to care about its content.</p><blockquote><p>i will fill this website sooner or later.</p></blockquote><figure class="highlight python"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br><span class="line">2</span><br><span class="line">3</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line"><span class="built_in">print</span>(<span class="string">&#x27;hello world!&#x27;</span>)</span><br><span class="line"><span class="keyword">for</span> i <span class="keyword">in</span> <span class="built_in">range</span>(<span class="number">5</span>):</span><br><span class="line">    <span class="built_in">print</span>(i)</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; class=&quot;aplayer-secondary-style-marker&quot; href=&quot;\assets\css\APlayer.min.css&quot;&gt;&lt;script src=&quot;\assets\js\APlayer.min.js&quot; cla</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="article" scheme="https://aryuze.github.io/tags/article/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>我之前出的英文题(原稿)</title>
    <link href="https://aryuze.github.io/2025/06/27/english_article/"/>
    <id>https://aryuze.github.io/2025/06/27/english_article/</id>
    <published>2025-06-27T12:31:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2025-06-27T13:34:01.905Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<link rel="stylesheet" class="aplayer-secondary-style-marker" href="\assets\css\APlayer.min.css"><script src="\assets\js\APlayer.min.js" class="aplayer-secondary-script-marker"></script><p>Read the passage, answer the following questions:<br>William once depicted a weird man in his bestseller The Moon and Sixpence. A man, a truly stranger to England society and the upper class he’s been living in. “A totally failure” would be the most accurate title that others give to him , unquestionably. Far from embracing the crowd’s expectations, he fled, not being knocked down but striking back to this dull life. He followed the real desire in his heart of reaching the height of art he’s been pursuing. And with a surprising but reasonable narrative of his artistic life, the whole story ended.<br>Indeed, it’s a sensation to English literature. Nevertheless, still there’s profound meaning going beyond its reputation therefore it is ought to be “unearthed”. As for me, I love these so-called “unrealistic” twists. Undeniably, William wanted to convey something through his masterpiece, but what’s that?<br>Never can we people suffer from constant wars, years of famine, or extreme poverty in this meta era we’re currently living in. With no exception we should’ve drown in infinite happiness. However, the truth is just the other way around. The mechanized, identical work, with the arranged work done and undone back and forth, has been forcing us to fit into the format of society, into the rules of others who intended to take advantages of you. Sooner or later, with blunted senses and obscured mind, we ultimately have to admit its destructive impact. Yes, we have lost ourselves. We don’t know where we’re heading for. And we’re also diminishing our possibilities to get to know our inner world. This is not kidding but a tangible phenomenon occurring in real time. Not before we realized have we been a loser confronting with the “ourselves”. What we wanted and what we pursue, remained a problem, developing as a barrier and preventing us from gaining our happiness and satisfaction of life.<br>I learned this serious matter several years ago and I’ve been calling others to “be ourselves”. That sounds crazy to teachers, parents even some students themselves. But we truly need that “moonlight” to cast on us, leading us to the right direction. We can’t act like a sitting duck. So from now on, turn off your phone, contemplate more and take your future serious. Flee from the laziness, the previous state of mind, and head towards what you’ve been dreaming of. Take myself for example, I would use my whole weekend to do computer programming, because I know that will develop into my lifelong career. I would spend the free time to refine my violin technique, for I understand music will be around me forever thus it’s essential to practice.<br>Some people would argue that they always feel down and exhausted. They burnt money to find “psychiatrists”. They wasted time to find the “effective antidote”. But that’s quite funny, all what they need is just look up to the sky. Because up there, it’s moonlight.</p><p>1.What is the main theme of William’s The Moon and Sixpence according to the author?<br>A) The success story of an upper-class man<br>B) A man’s rebellion against societal expectations to pursue art<br>C) The history of English literature<br>D) The importance of financial stability</p><p>2.The author mentions “mechanized, identical work” primarily to criticize:<br>A) Loss of individuality in modern society<br>B) Technological progress<br>C) The popularity of factory jobs<br>D) The education system</p><p>3.The word “tangible” in the phrase “a tangible phenomenon” most closely means:<br>A) Imaginary<br>B) Touchable<br>C) Real and observable<br>D) Temporary</p><p>4.The author uses the metaphor of “moonlight” to symbolize:<br>A) The happiness in life<br>B) Guidance to self-discovery and dream<br>C) The pursuit of artistic height<br>D) William’s masterpiece</p><p>Answer: B A C B</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;link rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; class=&quot;aplayer-secondary-style-marker&quot; href=&quot;\assets\css\APlayer.min.css&quot;&gt;&lt;script src=&quot;\assets\js\APlayer.min.js&quot; cla</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="daily" scheme="https://aryuze.github.io/tags/daily/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
